[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Applause]
[Applause]
The life insurance industry in Vietnam
is growing at a huge pace due to the
developing middle class, also growing at
a Rapid P
leader. We're very Quick, that's me. Lots and
lots of opportunities for everybody.
Opportunities
grow.
[Music]
Our company is
currently working in the business development cooperation department.
Starting as a management intern, Hoang has had the
opportunity to
work with different departments,
participate in large company projects, and
will soon be transferring for one
year to Fenal Malaysia. Hoang is very
excited about this opportunity to develop himself
and believes that Fenal will be the
right choice for you in your
future career development.
Everyone's opinion: what is Fenal? Convenient,
professional, unique, great,
your health, your career,
our opinions. We care.